solomon ayodele



solomonayodele65@gmail.com



+2347017095720



linkedin.com/in/solomon-ayodele-6b35571b2



https://solohcode.herokuapp.com

Summary

My name is Solomon Ayodele a look out entrepreneur and a full time frontend software application engineer with 5years of coding experience, 4 years of programming experience and 3 years of working experience in the use of web languages like HTML || CSS || JAVASCRIPT || REACT || FIGMA... in the frontend development field and UI/ UX designs and development, 2 years of backend development experience in the field of programming and web development with the skill and use of PHP || LARAVEL..., I have built and designed attractive and fully functional web applications for my desired clients, I have worked under two organizations now and still currently working for the second organization presently, and also into digital marketing, I've got a good sense of humor and am very good at team play also possesses good communication skill and a good team player, developed and completed more than three live projects, love to code play games and good music.

Experience

Freelance Software Engineer

Andela

Feb 2021 - Present (8 months +)

currently working as a freelancer software engineer on the andela platform.

p Freelance Web Developer

Upwork

Feb 2021 - Present (8 months +)

currently working as a freelancer on the upwork platform.

Freelance Web Developer

Fiverr

Aug 2019 - Present (2 years 2 months +)

currently working as a freelancer on the fiverr platform.

Frontend Developer

Techend Limited

Apr 2021 - Present (6 months +)

Currently working as a frontend software engineer under the Techend limited organization.

Frontend Developer

Techend inc

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021 (7 months)

worked as a frontend developer intern under the Techend Limited organization.

Web Designer

TJV foundation

Jul 2018 - Aug 2019 (1 year 2 months)

worked as an intern web designer under the TJV foundation, developed few projects using acceptable technologies and obtained certifications.

Education



Babs fafunwa millennium senior grammar school

SSCE, Physical Science and Tech 2017 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications



(Certification of soft skill training completion - Jobberman Nigeria 3637898



Certification of internship completion - TJV foundation

Skills

Project Management • Analytical Skills • Design • Leadership • Problem Solving • Teamwork • React.js • JavaScript • Git • Web Development

Honors & Awards



Second Place Best commited intern - Tiv Inc.

Aug 2019